Do you know there's an animal that can theoretically live forever?
Wait, seriously?
That sounds like something out of a fantasy novel.
What is it?
It's not a mythical beast at all, but a tiny jellyfish known as the Immortal Jellyfish.
Its scientific name is Turatopsis Dorny.
An immortal jellyfish?
That's incredible!
Where are these things found?
They're found in oceans all around the world.
And what makes them immortal is their remarkable survival skill.
What kind of skill are we talking about?
When faced with old age, injury, or even starvation, it doesn't just die.
It can reverse its entire life cycle, transforming back into its earliest stage, a polyp.
So it just becomes a baby again?
That's wild!
Does it then grow into a new jellyfish?
Exactly!
From that polyp, a new, genetically identical jellyfish will eventually grow!
Imagine a butterfly being able to turn back into a caterpillar and start its life all
over again!
Wow!
That's such a perfect analogy!
So scientists must be really interested in this, right?
Absolutely!
This unique ability to essentially cheat death has fascinated them.
They're studying it closely to unlock secrets about aging.
That makes sense.
A tiny creature deep in the ocean holding a potential key to immortality.
That's a pretty big deal.
Now I know.